Button, Daniel Evan; Papers apap231
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1965-1971; Undated; 5; 13.6 cubic ft.
  - Fargo, Francis F. - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Fatato, Lawrence - Immigration, 1966 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Favita, Stephen - Air Force, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Epps, J. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Erwin, John Milo - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Evans, Airman Alfred R. - Air Force, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Evans, David W. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Federal grant for city school district of Troy - Junior Technical School application, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Federation of Official Planning Organization - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Fehervan, Anthony J. - Department of Labor, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Ferber, William - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Ferguson, Stuart G. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Fernandez, Abel J. - Immigration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Ferraioli, Richard A. - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1967-1970 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Ferro, Domenick J. - Treasury Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Finger, John N. - Schenectady, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Fitzgerald, George - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Flannigan, Colonal William C., 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Flatt, Dean M. - Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1969 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Flavin Mrs. Robert J. - Schenectady, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Flowers, Paul - Immigration and National Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Foreman, William M., 1967; 1970 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Foster, Kenneth L. - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 28)
  - Francisco, Ralph - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 29)
  - Franklin, Peter, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 30)
  - Fredette, Wayne - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 31)
  - Galloway, Alexander T. - Department of Defense, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 32)
  - Garry, Harry, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 33)
  - Gathen, Larry C. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Gavin, James M., 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 35)
  - Gelinas, Dr. Allen R. - Immigration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 36)
  - Giluomo, Joseph - Patent Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 37)
  - Geoco, Joseph - Marines, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 38)
  - George, Fred - Navy, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 39)
  - Gerlach, David P., West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 40)
  - Giancaferino, Camillo - Immigration and National Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 41)
  - Giannetti, Irene - Schenectady, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 42)
  - Gillespie, Donald M. - Selective Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 43)
  - Glasser, William - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 44)
  - Glenck, Leslie F. - Social Security, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 45)
  - Glenn B. and Gertrude P. Warren Foundation, Inc., 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 46)
  - Glushko, Watter C. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1967-1968 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 47)
  - Glushko, William A. - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1967-1968 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 48)
  - Golub, William - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 49)
  - Good, Howard U. - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 50)
  - Goudreau, Donald F. - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 51)
  - Granato, Frank R. - Post Office Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 52)
  - Grand Coulee Dam Installation - Department of Interior, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 53)
  - Greek Military Junta, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 54)
  - Greene, Anthony - Internal Revenue Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 55)
  - Greiner, Raymond E. - Small Business Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 56)
  - Grisworld, Kenneth S. - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 57)
  - Grubar, Joseph - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 58)
  - Guilderland application for town park, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 59)
  - Hale, Patrick J. - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 60)
  - Hall, Keith - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 61)
  - Halloran, Daniel F. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 62)
  - Halloran, Daniel F. - national educational television, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 63)
  - Hanley, Frances - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 64)
  - Harnau, William - Defense, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 65)
  - Harris, Joseph - Navy Court of Claims, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 66)
  - Harrison, Steve - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 67)
  - Harrison II. Thomas M. - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 68)
  - Hart, Joyce C. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 69)
  - Hartheimer, Alberts - FWA, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 70)
  - Harvey, Chief Bernard H. - Navy, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 71)
  - Hawley, Chester L., 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 72)
  - Hawley, David Louis, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 73)
  - Helme, Frank L. - State Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 74)
  - Henry, Charles - Federal Aviation Agency, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 75)
  - Henry, Edna May - Bureau of Census, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 76)
  - Henzel, Rosa A. - Internal Revenue Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 77)
  - Hepp, Joseph - Service Academy - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 78)
  - Hodges, William D. - Air Force, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 79)
  - Hogan Camp, Marlene M. - Marine Corps, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 80)
  - Hogarth, Richard A. (Pastor), 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 81)
  - Hollner, Pfc Paul J. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 82)
  - Horn, Jacob E. - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 83)
  - Horsburgh, Captain Donald - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 84)
  - Horton, Dennis - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 85)
  - Houlihan, Daniel C., 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 86)
  - Housing Conference - White House, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 87)
  - Howgate, Dorthea - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 88)
  - Huff, Robert - Air Force, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 89)
  - Hughes, John R. - Navy, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 90)
  - Hughes, Mildred - Social Security Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 91)
  - Hull, Harding E. - Coast Guard, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 92)
  - Hunt, George, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 93)
  - Huppert, Alice - Department of Defense, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 94)
  - Hynes, James - Air Force, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 95)
  - Hynes, William C. - Immigration and National Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 96)
  - Insley, R.E. - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 97)
  - Jackson, Aaron C. - Social Security Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 98)
  - Janiszewski, Richard - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 99)
  - Jenkins, Lawrence A. - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 100)
  - Jensen, Stephen - Marines, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 101)
  - Johnson, Arthur - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 102)
  - Johnson, Linette - State Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 103)
  - Johnson, Margaret C. - Social Security Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 104)
  - Jones, Robert H. III, Esquire - HUAC, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 105)
  - Jopp, Kenneth B. - Social Security Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 106)
  - Jossi, Charles J. - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 107)
  - Juno, George W. Federal Trade Commission, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 108)
  - Jurusik, Frank - Internal Revenue Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 109)
  - Kaaris, Barend - State Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 110)
  - Kaidas, John V. - Veterans Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 111)
  - Kalil, Peter - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 112)
  - Kampf, John E. - Internal Revenue Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 113)
  - Kapcinski, Robert D. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 114)
  - Karichkowsky, Alex - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 115)
  - Karowski, Josephine - Social Security Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 116)
  - Keenan, Pvt. Charles W. - Marine Corps, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 117)
  - Kelleher, Robert M. - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 118)
  - Keller, Pfc. Arthur - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 119)
  - Kelly, Donald - Navy, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 120)
  - Kelly, Richard F. - Albany, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 121)
  - Kelman, Kenneth - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 122)
  - Kennedy, Christopher - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 123)
  - Kermani, Rustam K. - State Department, Iranian Embassy, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 124)
  - Ketz, Nicholas - bank failure, Cohoes, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 125)
  - Kling, David C. - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 126)
  - King, James R. - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 127)
  - King, John C. - Social Security, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 128)
  - Kirby, Kevin - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 129)
  - Kirwan, William E. - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 130)
  - Klemm, William R. - Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 131)
  - Knee, Richard A. - Coast Guard - [RESTRICTED], 1967-1968 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 132)
  - Knefley, Henry R. - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 133)
  - Knight, Paul - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 134)
  - Korman, Richard - Civil Service Commission, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 135)
  - Kostyniak, Paul - Selective Service System, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 136)
  - Kotzpin, Dr. Gerald - State Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 137)
  - Kouray, Christian X. - Federal Reserve System, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 138)
  - Koutelis, Michael James - Selective Service System, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 139)
  - Krantz, Karl T. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 140)
  - Kriwanek, T. Matthew, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1967-1968 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 141)
  - Kruetzfeldt, Grace Byrne - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 142)
  - Krywinski, Valerie - State Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 143)
  - Kuehn, Harry - Department of the Interior, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 144)
  - Kuza, Frederick M. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 145)
  - Labow, Dr. Stanley - Immigration and National Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 146)
  - Laden, Joseph - Department of Defense, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 147)
  - Laeyt, James - Marine Corps, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 148)
  - Larocque, Claudia - Marines, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 149)
  - La Salle Institute, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 150)
  - Latin, Samuel - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 151)
  - Lauber, Jack D. - Post Office, Schenectady, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 152)
  - Lawson, Gregory G. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 153)
  - Lawson, William B. - Vietnam Economics, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 154)
  - Lawton, Albert J. - Navy, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 155)
  - Layman, Donald L. - Marine Corps, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 156)
  - Le Gere, Robert - Civil Service Commission, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 157)
  - Leitner, Marc - New York State, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 158)
  - Letter to chiefs of policy re: Cahill - Railsback Amendment, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 159)
  - Levi, Richard - Tariff Commission, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 160)
  - Lewandowski, Maria - Immigration and National Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 161)
  - Lewthwaite, Gordon, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 162)
  - Liaricos, Dr. Sotiris - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 163)
  - Lichtenstein, Dr. Pearl - Post Office Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 164)
  - Linndsay, G. Carroll - General Services Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 165)
  - Linehan, Bernard - Post Office, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 166)
  - Lingard, Robert A. - Air Force Academy, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 167)
  - Linnehan, John J. II - Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 168)
  - Linville, Thomas M., 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 169)
  - Lito, Peter - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 170)
  - Livingston, Mrs. James A.- Internal Revenue Service - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 171)
  - Loftus, John R. - Merchant Marine - [RESTRICTED], 1967-1970 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 172)
  - Lombardi, Frank A. Sgt - Air Force, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 173)
  - Lord, Victor A., 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 174)
  - Lotz, Brian Jude - Service Academies - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 175)
  - Lownes, Richard - Air Force, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 176)
  - Lucowitz, Mary - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 177)
  - Ludwig, Robert J. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 178)
  - Macejka, Mattew - Small Business Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 179)
  - MacFarlane, Mark P. - Selective Service, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 180)
  - Maitino, Pfc Robert L. - Army, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 181)
  - Malebranche, Dr. Roger - Immigration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 182)
  - Mann, Viola - Veterans Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 183)
  - Manno, Mario T. - Immigration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 184)
  - Marchand, Paul J. - Selective Service - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 185)
  - Marks, Dave - Albany, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 186)
  - Markson, Ralph and Elizabeth - State Department, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 187)
  - Marmarines, Konstantinos - Immigration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 188)
  - Martin, James H. - General Service Administration, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 189)
  - Martin, William - Navy, 1967 (Box 2 (5-Case Files), Folder 190)
  - Maslanka, Thomas A. - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 1)
  - McAuliffe, John L. - Post Office Department, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 2)
  - McCabe, John F. - Post Office Department, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 3)
  - McCarthy, Gertrude R. - Social Security Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 4)
  - McCormacks Corners - Post Office, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 5)
  - McCullough, Harold - summer emplyoment, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 6)
  - McDermott, Joseph T. - Post Office, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 7)
  - McDougall, David Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1967-1970 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 8)
  - McFarland, Bruce N. - State Department, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 9)
  - McGinn, Lawrence - State Department, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - McGraw, Thomas C. - Service Committee, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 11)
  - McGuire, Ingeborg - Immigration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 12)
  - McKay, Katherine - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 13)
  - McKenna, Patrick - Civil Service Commission, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 14)
  - McKinlock, Kenneth - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 15)
  - McKinney, Laurence, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 16)
  - McKownville Improvement Association - Post Office, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 17)
  - McLaughlin, Mark G. - [RESTRICTED], 1967; 1970 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 18)
  - McMahon, Betty - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 19)
  - McMahon, Sgt. Joseph A. - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 20)
  - McNearney, William E. - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 21)
  - McPartlon, Dr. J. Peter - Schenectady, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 22)
  - McSherry, Raymond - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Mechanicville Urban renewal area - HUD, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Mehan, Captain Hugh B Jr. - Air Force, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Merriman, Kenneth F. - Navy, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Merriman, Kenneth - Post Office, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Meserzey, Pfc Donald - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 28)
  - Messerle, Pricate Douglas A. - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 29)
  - Messina, Gaetano - Immigration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 30)
  - Michalski, Daniel J. - Selective Service System, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 31)
  - Michaelson, Jesse, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 32)
  - Mincarelli, Timothy D. - Marines, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 33)
  - Mitchell, John W. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1968; Undated (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Mogul, Joan - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 35)
  - Mohawk Airlines file, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 36)
  - Molnar, Joseph - Internal Revenue Service, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 37)
  - Molt, Marinus - welfare Albany, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 38)
  - Mooney Edward A. - Judiciar Committee - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 39)
  - Moore, Mrs. John D. - Post Office, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 40)
  - Moran, Staff Sgt. - Air Force, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 41)
  - Morgenstern, Arthur - Public Health Service, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 42)
  - Morrett, Louis - Federal Communication Commission, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 43)
  - Moseley, Harry R. - Department of Labor, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 44)
  - Motta, Frank - Veterans Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 45)
  - Munsell, Edward C. - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 46)
  - Murnaghan, Richard C. - Post Office Department, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 47)
  - Murphy, William F. - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 48)
  - Murray, Lawrence - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 49)
  - Murray, William R. - Marines, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 50)
  - Myers, Evans A. - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 51)
  - NAACP Northeastern Region M State Conference, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 52)
  - Nailor, Norman N. - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 53)
  - Nardelli, Frank - State Department, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 54)
  - Nardiello, Charles J., 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 55)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers - Post Office Department, Troy, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 56)
  - National Association of Postal Supervisors of the Tri-City area, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 57)
  - Naughter, John J. - State Department/Immigration, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 58)
  - Navojosky, Arthur J. - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 59)
  - Neals, Edward Thomas - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 60)
  - Neddo, Eugene H. - Army, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 61)
  - Nelson Associates - Post Office, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 62)
  - New Scotland - youth center, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 63)
  - New York Federal Savings and Loan Associates, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 64)
  - Nichol, John I. - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 65)
  - Niskayuna High School, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 66)
  - Noiseux, Walter - Air Force, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 67)
  - Nolles, Lucas - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 68)
  - Norton, William R. - Army, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 69)
  - Not nominated, 1967; Undated (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 70)
  - Not nominated, encouraged to re-apply, 1967; Undated (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 71)
  - O'brien, Howard T. - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 72)
  - Occhino, Ida - Immigration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 73)
  - O'HARA, A.C., 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 74)
  - Oliver, John - Peace Corps, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 75)
  - O'Neil, Robert W. - Air Force, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 76)
  - Ordway, Jenny M. State Department, Japanese Embassy, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 77)
  - Osterhout, Laura - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 78)
  - Otwell, Thomas - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 79)
  - Owens, Thomas P. - Social Security Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 80)
  - Ozimek, Mrs. Thomas and McCall, Mrs. Robert - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 81)
  - Pajak, Penny - Department of Social Services, NY, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 82)
  - Palazini, Bruce - Marine Corps, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 83)
  - Palmer, Dolores - Treasury Department, Internal Revenue Service, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 84)
  - Palmer, Elizabeth M.D., 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 85)
  - Palmeter, Noel - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1967; 1969 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 86-87)
  - Palyswiat, Edward - Army, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 88)
  - Pappas, Peter C. - Selective Service, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 89)
  - Parente, Armando J. - Department of Defense, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 90)
  - Parker, Gary S. - Navy, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 91)
  - Parker, Margaret E. - Welfare, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 92)
  - Paska, Margery - Peace Corps, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 93)
  - Pattison, James H. - Air Force, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 94)
  - Paul, William L. - Air Force, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 95)
  - Pelicone, Frederick - Marine Corps - [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 96)
  - Perreault, Paul W. - Department of Labor, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 97)
  - Perry, Mrs. David - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 98)
  - Perry, Edward C., 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 99)
  - Petelchuk, Paul - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 100)
  - Peteler, Mr. and Mrs. - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 101)
  - Pettengill, Robert B. - Civil Defense, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 102)
  - Peters, Emil - Public Works, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 103)
  - Peterson, Eric - Immigration and National Service, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 104)
  - Pfeiffer, Ruth - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Case Files), Folder 105)